为啥我总是什么都找不到...
How come that I can never find anything...
因为你太邋遢了 阿朱
Because you're a slob, June.
因为你老是乱糟糟的...
because you are a disorganized...
哇哦! 饺子!
Ooh! Dumpling.
克洛伊?
Chloe?
干嘛?
What?!
有声音
I heard something.
废话! 你一直在叫"克洛伊! 克洛伊!"
Yeah! You screaming "Chloe! Chloe!"
声音还那么大!
at the top of your lungs!
啥玩意?
What was that?
惊喜!
Superise!
警报! 入侵! 警报! 入侵!
Nuts! Nose! Nuts! Nose!
泰迪!
Teddy!
没错就是我! 她听到的声音是我发出来的
It was me. I was the noise she was hearing.
泰迪是谁?
Who is Teddy,
为什么这有个房间 我从来没见过?
and w-what is this room that I've never seen before?
这是第三个卧室
Oh, that's our third bedroom.
我把它当壁橱用的
I use it as my closet.
我们小时候 泰迪和我一起
And Teddy and I went to psychopath camp together
参加过神经病夏令营!
when we were kids!
阿朱 我没跟你说过这个壁橱
June, I didn't tell you about the closet,
我不该瞒着你的
and that's a big thing to keep from somebody.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
见到你真是太高兴了!
It's so good to see you!
我要狠狠地抱你下!
I'm gonna give you a back crack!
抱! 抱!
Back crack! Back crack!
# 我并不完美 不打小报告 #
I'm not perfect, I'm no snitch
# 但要告诉你 她是个... #
but I can tell you she's a...
这一整个房间都用来放衣服?
This whole room is for your clothes?
我还把套装塞在防火梯那边的垃圾袋里
I keep my suits in a trash bag on the fire escape.
麻冷者夏令营
Camp C.U.T.S.
麻冷者代表"麻木冷酷的幸存者"
it stands for "Callous Unemotional Trait Survivors."
你还留着这件汗衫?
You kept the shirt?
我当然留着啦
Of course I kept the shirt.
我太爱那里了
I loved it there.
我们一起唱营歌吧?
Should we sing her the camp song?
我们乃是正常孩童
We are normal children.
我们不会虐待动物
We don't torture animals.
尊重治疗师 好好吃下药
Respect your therapist. Take your meds.
我们的痛苦终将消失
Our pain is hopefully finite.
我妈妈把我送去麻冷者夏令营的
My mom sent me to camp C.U.T.S.
因为她觉得我无法表达感情
Because she thought I had trouble expressing any emotion.
我对此没有任何感想
I had no reaction to that.
我妈妈送我去是因为我对我哥做的事
And my mom sent me because of what I did to my brother.
你对你哥哥做了什么?
What'd you do to your brother?
每年 泰迪都会停一段药
So every year, Teddy goes off his meds,
到镇上来参加卡特沼泽商店大甩卖
and he comes to town for the Carter Marsh warehouse sale.
不嗑药的泰迪真是人才
Unmedicated Teddy is exactly what I need to help
我要他帮忙赶走那些从康乃狄克州驾车
fend off the vicious women from Connecticut
远道而来参加年度最大甩卖的坏女人
who S.U.V. In for the biggest sale of the year.
你听到了么 阿朱
Can you hear them, June,
她们磨枪擦剑
preparing for battle,
准备战斗的号角声?
sharpening their fingernails?
我想买这条裙子
This is the dress that I want.
平时零售价四千美元
Retail value is $4,000.
现在只要399美元
They'll mark it down to $399.
那儿只有一件 而且店家会把它藏起来
They'll only have one, and they'll hide it...
但我会找到它的
but I'll find it.
那泰迪做什么?
What does Teddy do?
他为我扫清道路 开辟战场
He clears a path and erects a force field.
我很强悍 阿朱 但我需要一位战士
I'm tough, June, but I need a warrior...
悍勇无畏的战士
someone with no fear.
你已经无所畏惧了
You were the fearless one.
你把吴小姐从冰淇淋车里面推出来
You pushed Miss.Wu out of the ice cream truck
还用汽水浇了我们一身
and threw us all bomb pops.
吴小姐动作太慢了 必须得推她出来
Wu was slow. She had to be pushed.
天哪! 那个夏令营太棒了 真可惜不在了
God! That camp was the best. It's so sad that it's gone.
怎么回事?
What happened to it?
- 被烧掉了 - 关门了
- It burned down. - Closed.
你现在怎么样?有几个男人围着你转啊?
And so what about you? How many guys in your rotation?
七个
Seven.
但只有一个她真心喜欢!
But she only loves one!
阿朱 闭嘴!
June, shut up!
- 真的? 那人谁? - 那人叫班吉b
- She does? Who is he? - His name is Benjamin.
他导演了部佳作 由詹姆斯出演
He directed a wonderful movie that James was in
叫做"爱的怪怪"
called "Love Monster."
- 从没听过 - 他们在万圣节认识
- Never heard of it! - They met on Halloween,
她自认为戏耍了班吉b
and she thought she was playing a trick on him,
事实正相反
but it turned out he was playing a trick on her,
在机场他们演了出狗血剧
and they had a romantic scene at the airport
此后再没联系过
and they haven't talked to each other since.
不好意思 你上衣里边是什么?
Excuse me. What is going on under your top?
呃 是件泳衣
It's a, uh, it's a bathing suit.
啊! 恶魔!
Aah! Devil!
干嘛? 最近工作太忙了
What? It's been really crazy at work,
我没时间洗衣服了
and I haven't had time to do laundry.
阿朱 如果你想和我们一起去大甩卖
June, if you wanna come with us to the warehouse sale,
我也愿意为你而战
I'd be happy to block for you, too.
你人真好 泰迪
That's very sweet, Teddy,
但我不需要买新的漂亮内衣
but I don't need any new fancy underwear.
阿朱 要是因为穿泳衣得了尿路感染
June, you deserve that urinary tract infection
纯属活该
that bathing suit's giving you.
你说我们能以贵宾身份进来 我没料到是这样
When you said we had a VIP access, I pictured the exact opposite of this.
不勘探战地 怎能上战场 詹姆斯
You can't go to war if you don't know the battlefield, James.
这场大甩卖唯一的好处
the only good thing about this sale
就是它让旗舰店变成了世外桃源
is the xanadu it creates at the flagship store.
当你们这些女人在这里大战的时候
While you guys are here battling it out,
我在住宅区安静地享受购物时光
I will be uptown shopping in peace.
我还要去看看比克牌牛仔裤卖得怎么样
I'll even check in on how the Beek jeans are selling.
一般我就帮基佬小情侣
I usually end up signing a couple pairs
在裤子上签点名
for young homosexual tourists.
快看! 那边就是康乃狄克团
Oh, look! There they are, the Connecticut crew,
还因为拼车过来大汗淋漓着呢
still all sweaty from the carpool ride in.
带头儿的还真是够放纵自己的啊
Oh, the ringleader's really let herself go.
嘿 海瑟 嗨!
Hey, Heather! Hi!
你胖死了
You're fat!
- 克洛伊 那个女的怀孕了 - 我知道
- Chloe, that woman is with child. - I know.
嘿 海瑟!
Hey, Heather!
祝你周六时能顺利把肥臀挪过来
Good luck dragging your fat ass around here on Saturday.
我的名字叫绯斯
My name is Faith,
我还知道他们把这件藏哪儿了
and I know just where they'll stash it.
我的裙子!
Oh! My dress.
我去把她们轮胎放掉气
I'm gonna go flatten their tires.
詹姆斯 你最近怎么样?
So,James, what's up with you?
为了某个电视剧试映 我和海伦・亨特
Uh, I passed on a chemistry read with Helen Hunt
一起读了点化学资料
for some TV pilot.
嗯哼 还有呢?
Uh-huh. What else?
我二表姐简妮特爱上我了
My second cousin Janet is in love with me.
她抱我的方法很有问题
Her hugs remain wildly inappropriate.
嗯哼 还有呢?
Uh-huh. What else?
你干嘛不直接问我?
Why don't you just ask me?
问你什么?
Ask you what?
班吉b怎么样
How Benjamin's doing.
班吉b谁啊?
Who Benjamin?
克洛伊 你们明明彼此喜欢
Chloe, you guys obviously like each other.
你们自从万圣节后还没讲过话呢
You haven't talked since halloween.
你为什么不打给他?
Why don't you just call him?
要我来主动? 没门
And be the first one to make the second move? No way.
克洛伊 你喜欢他 别玩了
Chloe, you like this guy. Stop playing games.
他不在纽约 可我肯定他愿意听....
He's out of town, but I'm sure he would love to hear...
- 实战演练 - 噢!
- Practice drill! - Oh!
该死 詹姆斯!
Damn it, James!
别再用臭班吉b让我分心了
Stop distracting me with your weird Benjamin obsession!
我需要专注!
I have to focus!
这是我人生最重要的一周
This is the most important week of my life.
约翰・古德曼?!
John Goodman?!
约翰・古德曼在贵宾通道吗?
is John Goodman at the V.I.P. Walk-Through?
不 那只是海瑟
Oh! No, that's just Heather.
只是海瑟罢了 各位!
It's just Heather, everyone!
不用拍照 也不用凑过来签名啦
No autographs. Don't run up to her with a pen.
这人可没演"罗斯安家庭生活"
This person was not on "Roseanne."
稍等片刻! 去下洗手间!
Be right back! Gotta use the ladies'!
烦人的泳衣
Frickin' bathing suit.
我可没时间管你啊
I do not have time for this.
该死!
damn it!
我入伙了
I'm in.
我要去大甩卖
I wanna go to that sale.
好! 要谨记...
Yay! Okay, just remember...
头发扎起来 紧身衣穿上
Hair in a bun, no loose clothing.
为什么?
Why?
弱点! 弱点! 弱点!
Access point! Access point! Access point!
啊! 你不知道这是夹上的嘛!
Ow! You didn't know those were clip-Ons!
- 弱点! - 啊!
- Access point! - Ow!
- 弱点! 弱点!  - 知道啦!
- Access point! Access point! - I get it!
惊喜哟
Surprise.
班吉b!
Benjamin!
你来看我啦
You came to see me.
那就证明是你先主动的哦
That means you made the first second move.
呃 抱歉 我不是来看你的
Uh, no. Sorry, I'm not here to see you.
我来给小詹送惊喜礼物 在意大利买的呢
I'm here to surprise jimbo with a gift I bought him in Italy.
你给我买礼物了?
You got me a present?
可你认为我先主动联系了
But you thinking I made the first second move
用实际行动证明你先主动了
is actually you making the first second move.
什么?
Uh, what?
不 我...
No, I...
班吉b 我是泰迪 泰迪 真高兴见到班吉b
Benjamin, Teddy. Teddy, Benjamin.
- 克洛伊和我 - 他是阿朱的男朋友!
- Chloe and I went to... -  He's June's boyfriend!
他... 他刚想说
He was... He was gonna say,
"克洛伊和我是...阿朱的男朋友"
"Chloe and I went... to June's boyfriend."
摸摸这 摸摸这
hoke hoke
亲爱的 放松点
Relax honey.
阿朱 我要你假装和泰迪约会
June, I need you to pretend to date Teddy.
要是班吉b知道我太多往事
If Benjamin knows too much about me,
他会用那些爆料伤害我
he'll just use it against me as ammunition...
就跟你跟我说你尿床后
The same way you told me you used to wet the bed,
我都把你叫尿尿龙一样
and now I refer to you as "Pee Dragon."
你要让我和你那个停了药的疯子朋友
You're asking me to pretend-date your mentally unstable friend
假装约会
who is currently off his meds.
拜托 阿朱 那是泰迪 他没事的
Come on! June, it's Teddy. He's fine.
我为你而来 伊莱
I'm coming for you, Eli.
放马过来吧 泰迪
Bring it, Teddy.
看吧? 伊莱喜欢他
See? Eli loves him.
求你了 阿朱? 求你了求你了嘛
Please, June? Please? Please? Please? Please? Please? Please?
既然你承认我说的对
Well. Since you are basically admitting that I'm right
也像我期待一般深爱班吉b 那我...
and you love Benjamin as much as I want you to, I...
泰迪!
Teddy!
你要假装和尿尿龙约会了
You have to pretend to date  "Pee Dragon"
我能带面具吗?
Can I wear a Mask?
- 不行 - 那成了
- No. - I'm in.
- 不行 - 嘿 这里怎么样啊?
- No. - Hey. What's going on in here?
呃 我们只是在...
Uh, we w-we were just, uh...
在摸胸
we're boob-feeling.
让我们四人约会吧
Let's all go on a double date.
克洛伊
Chloe,
你朋友让我们四人约会
your friend just suggested a double date...
他们刚和你在厨房悄悄讲小话
Your friend you've been whispering with
是不是证明你想和我出去呀
here in the kitchen. You wanna go out with me.
不 我不想 我其实不想让你去
No, I don't. I actually don't want you to go.
我可不会因为你不想我就不去
Well, I'm not gonna not go because you don't want me to.
我也不会因为你不想让我去 我就不去
Well, I'm not going to not go because you don't want me to.
阿朱 我们去哪?
June, where are we going?
不不 别告诉他们
I-- No, don't tell them yet.
别告诉他们 不要嘛
W-- don't tell them yet. No.
这个小电影已经席卷全球了吧
That little movie's taken over the world, huh?
是啊
Yep.
我到现在还挑牙齿的粉毛毛呢
I think I'm still picking pink fur out of my teeth.
那好 小詹詹
so, jim jimbo
你最近怎么样啊?
what's going on with you?
我新装了个浴盆
I, uh, just got a new bidet installed.
嗯哼 还有呢?
Uh-huh. What else? Yeah.
我前几天和送信的姑娘狠打了一架
I had a crazy fight with my mail lady the other day.
还有呢?
Uh-huh. What else?
你为什么不直接问我?
Why don't you just ask me?
问你什么?
Ask you what?
克洛伊最近怎么样啊
What's going on with Chloe.
我有点厌倦夹在
I'm tired of being in the middle
你俩中间了
of your guys' relationship.
什么? 我们俩又没在一起
W-What? W-We're not in a relationship.
得了吧 别玩了
Come on, stop the games.
听着 克洛伊不擅长主动
Listen, Chloe's not good at making the first move,
尤其是对心动对象
Especially if it's in the right direction.
所以单刀直入咯 她也会的
But just cut the nonsense, and she will, too.
我保证
I promise you.
你是说...
You mean, just...
认真的?
be real?
我知道听起来很傻 可是管用
I know it sounds crazy, but it works.
就像拍电影
It's like in the movie,
当我看那些老套怪兽的时候
when I had to look past all the monster stereotypes
我只挑了普林可
and just see plinko for plinko.
你真会选 哥们
you know how to choose an incredible friend
谢了
Thank you.
不客气
Any time.
当然他会迟到了 耀武扬威嘛
Of course he's late. It's a power move.
我人模人样穿戴好坐着等他 就是个白痴
And I'm sitting here with my hand up my dress like a jerk.
为什么我们来这么早? 才五点啊
Why are we here so early? It's only 5:00.
我还不饿呢 午饭还没消化
I'm not hungry yet. I still feel lunch.
因为我们必须八点半上床睡觉
Because we have to go to bed at 8:30.
明早六点必须准时到仓库里
We need to be at the warehouse at 6:00 a.m. Sharp.
泰迪在哪?
Where's Teddy?
这是我们的 我们先坐下来的
This is ours. We were seated first,
可你却先有了面包 不公平
but you got bread first, and that's not fair.
我爱你
I love you.
好嘞 好嘞
Oh. Okay. Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
高招嘛
Well played.
故意来晚 显示权威
Showing up late, establishing your dominance.
不玩了 克洛伊 我去你家
No more games, Chloe. I came by your apartment
是想给你惊喜 不是詹姆斯
because I wanted to surprise you, not James.
其实我在洛杉矶还推掉了一场重要会议
Actually...  I blew off big meeting I had in l.A.
因为我想过来看你
Because I wanted to come here and see you
因为我想你
because I missed you.
什么情况?
What's happening?
我看他只是实话实说罢了
I-I think he's just being honest with you.
也许你也...也该这样?
Maybe you can-- you can do the same?
我跟泰迪有一腿
I'm having an affair with Teddy.
什么?
What?
阿朱 实在抱歉以这种方式通知你
June, I'm really sorry you had to find out this way.
如果你想大哭一场 厕所里就有张沙发
If you need to have an ugly cry, there's a Couch in the bathroom.
克洛伊 我一直对你都非常坦诚
Uh, Chloe, I was just totally honest with you,
我没有...
so I don't get--
你没有什么?
what don't you get?
我和泰迪有一腿 阿朱马上就要大哭一场
I'm having an affair with Teddy, and June's about to ugly cry.
阿朱 让他看看你的哭腔
Come on, June, give them a little preview.
就像...
It's like...
我这么可爱怎么学得像呢
I can't do it because I'm too cute.
泰迪 走吧
Teddy, let's go.
嘿! 我在彻底检查明日战鞋的性能
Hey!  I'm testing out my shopping heels for tomorrow.
- 你到底在搞什么? - 怎么了?
- What the hell was that? - What?
班吉b终于对你说了实话
Benjamin was finally being honest with you,
而你却对他撒了弥天大谎?
and you tell him this big, huge lie?
他说 "别再玩了"的时候
Well, the second he said "No more games,"
我瞬间觉得很无聊
I got instantly bored.
我发现 这就是我喜欢的他唯一理由
I realized that's the only reason I was into him,
所以 我放弃了
so I got out of it.
我才不相信呢
I don't believe you.
他终于对你说了实话
I think he finally started being honest with you,
但你却害怕了 所以拒绝了他
and you got scared and you bailed.
就像现在这样 你在逃跑
That's what you do. You run.
我才没有
No, I don't.
泰迪 你能跟她讲讲理吗?
Teddy, will you please talk some sense into her?
你也知道 我不太喜欢伊莱
As you can see, I don't really like Eli.
你干什么 泰迪兄? 扔我的煎饼吗?
What are you gonna do, Tedford? Flip my pancakes?
祝你拥有十尺长的胳膊!
Hope you have 10-Foot long arms!
不许叫我"泰迪熊"
Stop calling me "Tedford."
别再暗恋他了
Stop secretly Loving it!
顺便说一句 我们得晚餐在这了
These are our full dinners, by the way.
我和班吉b聊得很不开心
I had to have a very uncomfortable chat with Benjamin
所以把晚餐全打包了
as they were boxed up.
她当真? 这只是一场游戏吗?
I mean, is she serious? Is this a game?
我 我不知道 我真的不知道
Yeah, I-I don't know.  I don't know.
嗨 你能...你能把面包也装起来吗?
Hi. Um, can you just--can you just wrap up this bread for us
- 快点? 谢谢 - 没问题
- really quickly? Thank you. - Sure.
对不起 能再多给我们一点
And also I'm sorry. Can we have, um, a little extra dressing
这么点就可以了 谢谢
in, like, in a little one of these? Thank you. Yeah.
能给我们一堆叉子吗?
And can we--can we have a bunch of forks?
很多叉子
Too many forks. Yeah.
我不知道 我不知道
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know.
随便
Okay, Well, whatever.
我们明天早晨六点整就得起床
We have to be up tomorrow at 6:00 a.M. Sharp.
你不能抗拒自己的感觉
You can't avoid your feelings,
就想我没办法抗拒春卷一样!
just like I can't avoid the spring rolls!
春卷太好吃了 他们还送了酱油
'cause they're delicious and they gave me soy sauce
我真是太高兴了
and I'm so happy.
快起床! 我们迟到了!
Wake up! We're late!
闹钟定了下午 不是上午!
I did p.m. Instead of a.m.!
起床了! 我去叫出租车
wake up! I'm gonna go get a cab.
今日要大战康乃狄克州人!
it's a bad day to beat for Connecticut!
你觉得把闹钟定错时间
Do you think maybe it is possible you set your alarm wrong
可能是因为满脑子班吉b吗?
Because you were thinking about Benjamin?
阿朱 别开玩笑了!
June, don't be ridiculous!
泰迪 清空通道!
Teddy, clear the entrance!
这边! 开始了!
This way! Go time!
我是说 昨晚你可能受到了影响
I'm just saying, maybe last night had an effect on you.
闭嘴! 闭嘴! 我都没和那男人上过床
Shut up! Shut up! This is way too much talking
你说的太多了!
about a guy I haven't even had sex with!
我们都没接过吻 除了万圣节开玩笑那次
We haven't even kissed, except for a part of a halloween trick.
你甚至没有真正接过吻 你就这么喜欢他?
You haven't even real kissed, and you like him this much?
更证明你爱他!
Further proof of love!
要不是我们迟到了 天哪
If we weren't late, so help me god,
我会转过身 把你推下楼梯!
I would turn around and push you down this flight of stairs!
这次先记在账上!
I owe you one push down one flight of stairs!
距衣架还有三分钟! 快走!
Three minutes to rack! Let's go!
救命
Help me
更衣室在哪儿?
Where are the changing rooms?
你在浪费宝贵时间!
You're wasting precious time!
天啊 这些人真疯狂
Oh, my gosh. These people are crazy.
我还穿着呢!
I'm still wearing it!
下去! 下去!
Aah! Go down! Go down!
您喝茶吗?
Tea?
不用 谢谢了
Um, no. No. Thank you.
你知道吗?
Actually, you know what?
我还是喝点茶吧
I will have some tea.
真漂亮
This is nice. Ooh!
真可爱
This is lovely.
我今天什么都拿不到! 我到底是怎么了!
Ah! I can't get anything today! What is wrong with me?!
是班吉b!
it's Benjamin!
你喜欢班吉b!快滚!
You like Benjamin! Get away! Mm!
我要买吗? 原价是八百刀 减到四十五
Should I get this? It's $800, marked down to $45.
- 当然! - 好的
- Yes! - Okay.
我扭伤了膝盖!
I strained my knees!
- 你还好吗? - 声东击西! 谁派你来的?!
- Oh, no. Are you okay? - Diversion tactic! Who sent you?!
我的祖母!
My grandmother!
- 她到底想要什么?! - 那件夹克衫!
- What does she want?! - that jacket!
别做梦了!
Never!
- 专心! - 我正在努力!
- Focus! - Aah! I'm trying!
我正在努力!
I'm trying!
海瑟?
Heather?
我今天抢到了两个宝贝衣服
I'm getting two precious babies today.
我把广告册忘了 把你的给我!
I forgot my reference photo. Give me yours!
我家衣服在哪块?
Where's my boutique?
您说什么?
Excuse me?
比克牛仔时装
The Beek jeans boutique.
你移到商店前面去了吗?
Did you move it to the front of the store?
范德・比克先生...
Oh, Mr. Van der Beek...
他们畅销过一阵
They were selling really well,
但续订时定的太多...
but then we just reordered too many, and...
所以 减价卖给了
they've been remaindered...
商场大甩卖
to the warehouse sale.
不会吧
No
你在做什么?!
What are you doing?!
这次真不错
It's nice day provided
还能在这个地方 歇歇脚松口气
with this great chill-out corner just to relax and unwind and--
不不不! 这可不是你们歇脚的地方!
No, no, no! This isn't-- this isn't a place to relax!
这里也有战斗
This is--Fight here, too!
这些牛仔裤都特别好 你们想买的
Come on, these are great jeans. You want these.
看 她买了 她也买了!
Look, she's got em. Now she's got 'em!
啊! 绯斯? 绯斯?
Aah! Faith? Faith?
我在找一个刚刚生过孩子的女人 绯斯?
I'm looking for a woman who's just given birth? Faith?
你在找这些!
You're looking for these!
你知道吗?
Did you know about this?
我家牛仔裤被廉价出售了...
We've been remaindered. Uh...
女士 你知道... 她在流鼻血
madam, can I interest you in a p--Her nose is bleeding.
她流鼻血了 她居然不在乎
Her nose is bleeding. She didn't even care.
班吉b又打我电话了
Okay, this is Benjamin calling me again.
你对他做了什么?
What did you do to him?
- 我才不关心 - 她骗人!
- I don't care. - Don't let her fool you!
这是我的! 她很在乎!
Mine! She does care!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 把衣服给我! - 你给我松手!
- Aah! Give it to me! - Let go of it!
- 做梦! - 你这么胖! 你都穿不上!
- No! - You're not even a size zero! You can't even wear this!
我今早刚生完孩子 我无所不能
I had a baby this morning. You have no idea what I can do.
泰迪!
Teddy!
绯斯? 跟我回医院给孩子喂奶
Faith? Come back to the hospital and breastfeed our baby.
去休息区等着 克莱格!
Go wait in the relaxation corner, Craig!
那不是休息区!
It's not a relaxation corner!
是比克牛仔专卖区 比克牛仔耐穿又时尚
They're Beek jeans, and they're both durable and stylish.
我来了!
Incoming!
泰迪 快帮忙!
Teddy, help me!
抢到手了!
Ah! Yes!
他妈的太棒了! 太棒了!
Damn yes! Yes!
该死的!
Oh, god. Uhh!
我到底是怎么了?
What is wrong with me?
她很弱的
She was weak.
我本可以对她... 拳打脚踢
I could've... bitten her or scratched her
或是直接生挠硬拽
or just pushed her and kicked her.
我知道她的弱点在哪
I know she has tender areas now.
从来没有我抢不到的衣服
I never let a dress go.
也许是因为你有
Maybe that's because
比那件衣服更想要得到的东西
there's something you want more than that dress,
比如说班吉b 我熟悉你这种眼神
like Benjamin. I know that look in your eyes.
七年级时我一想到艾伦・德迈亚 我就这样
I had that same look in Seventh grade over Aaron Demayo.
一堆妞等着做他女朋友
His schedules never lined up.
# 麻冷者夏令营 #
Camp C.U.T.S.
# 让你卸下心防＃
Let your guard down
看他轻而易举的解开数学题和科学题
I saw him briefly on the stairs on the way to math and science.
# 情绪十分美妙 #
Emotions are good
一整天我都心不在焉
but I'd spend the rest of the day distracted,
一直在想他...
thinking about him...
# 人类都会改变 #
people Can change
# 不管报告如何 #
despite what all the research says
总犯低级错误 写错字啊
making easy mistakes like spelling "Separate" Wrong...
# 人类总能改变 #
people can change
家政课上标错火腿名称啊
or, you know, mismarking a hem in home ec.
# 人类总能改变 #
# People can change #
这都是喜欢一个人的征兆 克洛伊
that's what happens when you like somebody, Chloe.
倒霉
Crap.
嗨
Hi.
你来这干什么?
What are you doing here?
我骗了你
I lied to you.
我没有在和泰迪约会
I'm not having an affair with Teddy,
阿朱也没有
and June's not dating him.
这一切都是我编的
I made all that up
为了隐瞒我和泰迪是老朋友
so I could hide how Teddy and I really know each other.
我们一起去过神经病夏令营
We went to psychopath camp together.
什么地方?
What?
通常
Which, usually,
我会自豪的告诉那些大街上碰到的陌生人
I'll proudly tell any stranger I meet on the street,
但我没跟你说...
but I didn't tell you...
因为我很清楚 我在乎你对我的看法
Because clearly, I care what you think about me.
我是说 我很在乎
I mean, clearly I do.
看看我在大甩卖里抢到了什么
Look how I did at the warehouse sale.
那是什么?
What is that?
暖腿套和铁锹杰克的工具包
A leg warmer and a dopp kit from Jack spade.
一团糟
I failed.
都是你的错
And it's all your fault
因为很显然 我喜欢你
because, obviously, I really like you.
是啊 说的对 是很明显
Uh, Yeah. Yeah, obviously.
你昨晚在餐馆向我吐露心声时
Well, when you got all honest with me at the restaurant,
我惊慌失措 事情就变成这样了
I freaked out, and it became this whole thing,
然后阿朱穿着泳衣大吃了一顿
and then June ate a lot of food in a swimsuit.
但是一想到再也见不到你了...
But the thought of not seeing you again...
在过去的几个月里
In just these past few months
我看到了很多事情 想要和你分享
I saw so many things I wanted to tell you about.
我看到了患妥瑞症的送信员
I saw a bike messenger with tourette's,
争论坐哪班地铁回住宅区的瘾君子
two junkies arguing about which subway to take uptown.
争论琐事的瘾君子
Junkies arguing over mundane things
是我最喜欢的纽约一角
is one of my favorite things about New York.
我知道! 我也是!
I know! Mine, too!
克洛伊 我才不在乎你小时候去过神经病夏令营
Chloe, I don't care that you went to crazy camp as a kid.
你会在乎我参加过减肥营吗?
God, do you care that I went to fat camp?
很多次还是只有一次 还是...
You mean, like, for a lot of summers or just one or...
你吻起来真像个胖小子
You kiss like a fat kid.
你吻起来真像个疯子
You kiss like a crazy person.
# 啊 啊 啊 #
# Ahh, ahh, ahh #
不会吧!
No!
这些都是比克牛仔裤?
are those all Beek jeans?
是的 我知道为什么没人疯抢我的牛仔裤了
Yeah. I figured out why people weren't fighting over my jeans.
不是牛仔裤的问题 是我的问题
It's not the jeans' fault. It's my fault.
瞧 我设计了一款全球最棒的牛仔裤
See, I let a great pair of jeans out in the world
却没有设计能搭配的衬衫还有腰带
without a great shirt and a belt to set them off.
所以我要开创一条完整的服装生产线
So I'm gonna start a whole clothing line
就叫经典潮流比克
called le Beek chic C'est Beek.
名字我还想着呢
I'm still working on the name.  Mm-hmm.
耶! 你们俩在一起啦!
Yay! You're together!
没有
No.
班吉b要去洛杉矶 拍几个月的电影
Benjamin is going to l.A. For a few months to do a movie.
托夫・格雷斯出演教师的角色 太逊了
Topher grace plays a schoolteacher. Boo.
所以我们还是顺其自然吧
so we're gonna keep it casual.
阿朱 你买的什么
June, what did you do?
这条裤子二十八刀　纯皮的哦
Those pants were $28 for leather.
我对买到的物品很满意
I am so happy with All my purchases.
泰迪太给力了
And Teddy was amazing.
哦! 他睡着了
Oh! He's asleep.
一定是新药发挥药效了
His new meds must have kicked in.
再见了 营友 明年见了
Bye, camp friend. See you next year.
对了! 我们没能帮你把裙子抢回来
Oh! We couldn't get your dress back.
作为刚生完孩子的女人
Faith is surprisingly strong for a woman who has
绯斯的力气出奇的大
mesh underwear holding her uterus together.
但我们还是设法给你弄到了...
But we did manage to get you...
这个
this.
排队结账的时候剪掉的
Cut it off in the checkout line.
是左边的袖子!
It's the left sleeve!
她的衣服被毁了!
Her dress is ruined!
你们真是太棒了!
You guys are amazing!
抱抱!
Whoo! Back crack!
这个周五看鲨鱼箱了吗?
Did you see shark tank on Friday?
天啊 太激烈了
Oh, my god. So intense.
你周末跑去大甩卖了 阿朱?
You check up the wareshop sale this weekend, June?
是啊! 我去了
Yeah! Actually, I did.
你也去了吗?
Did you, too?
买到了几件不错的衣服
Found some great stuff.
噢 有点...
Oh, just...
褶子
Ruffles.
期待明年的大甩卖
Can't wait till next yeer.